#### Contact

eiroljan19@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/eirol-coronado-56a8892b1 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Git

React.js

**Firebase** 

# **Eirol Coronado**

Web Developer

Davao, Davao Region, Philippines

## Summary

Hello there! I'm Eirol Jan Coronado, a passionate Web Development . I thrive on creative works as Web Developer.

I hold a degree in Information Technology from University of the Immaculate Conception , where I honed my skills in HTML,CSS and frameworks. Over the years, I've gained valuable experience in my work that created a website and creating a corporate websites and ecommerce websites

Outside of work, you'll often find me social media. I believe in the importance of Embrace the present moment and make the most of every opportunity for joy and fulfillment.

I'm excited to continue expanding my knowledge and skills in Web Development, pushing the boundaries of what I thought possible and making meaningful contributions along the way.. Feel free to send or message me on my email.

Thank you for stopping by, and I look forward to connecting with you!

### Experience

RWeb Solutions Web Developer

CodeVision

Web Developer

April 2023 - December 2023 (9 months)

Collaborate with UI/UX designers to create user-friendly interfaces and ensure seamless integration with existing systems.

Created APIs using Node.js and Laravel that involve setting up routes, controllers, models, and handling data accordingly

Developed and implemented the quality standards and best practices,

contributing ideas and effort toward continuous improvement

Work on enhancing and maintaining existing software systems, implementing new features, and addressing performance issues.

Design and develop robust software applications from scratch, ensuring highquality and scalable solutions.

Conduct thorough testing and debugging to identify and fix software bugs, ensuring optimal performance.

Develop end-to-end web applications, including both front-end and back-end components, from conceptualization to deployment.

Collaborated with team members to define application requirements

Collaborated with the senior developer to enhance and learn new skills and experiences

MinNa LProc Mobile Developer March 2022 - May 2022 (3 months)

MinNa is a research and development laboratory established to work on the development of Natural Languages

FS Tech
Web development
November 2018 - December 2018 (2 months)

### Education

University of the Immaculate Conception Information Technology, Information Technology